(THE YARNS)
Do you happen to know this person?
Including this person.
This person was the one who posted the clip
of Sky throwing rocks at her friend's head.
You must expel her, Director.
I won't allow it.
Nattha, the parent who had
an issue with Miss Sookwan
She made Sky resign from the school.
Keep Sky safe and then
keep an eye on Miss Sookwan.
The body of a young woman was found
brutally murdered with dismemberment.
The victim wasn't a teacher.
Or did we solve the riddle wrong?
This yarn doesn't have a code.
You're stupid.
Now you're just a loser murderer.
Look!
Her life depends on you guys.
Sky.
This police officer will watch over you
instead of me.
He will follow you from a distance
and not interfere with you at all.
Are you okay with that?
And where are you going, officer?
Are you not going to learn decoding anymore?
Let's say tomorrow.
I'll come back to continue studying tomorrow.
Yes, you can continue studying tomorrow.
- Sky will go to the store first.
- Alright.
Sergeant, follow her from a distance. Don't be too close.
-She's not used to it yet. I'll leave her to you.
-Understood.
Hey!
Shit!
Hello, what's up?
- Lieutenant, Sky was kidnapped!
- Huh? What?
I was walking behind her and she was
kidnapped into a van.
Where is Sky now?
Look!
This is the new victim
that I'm going to kill.
Is this enough evidence?
Look!
Stop moving or I'll kill you live on TV!
Her life depends on you guys.
Sky!
Aren't you? Aren't you? Aren't you?
If you're really competent,
come save her in time.
You have twelve hours.
If you think that
I'm looking down on you guys,
I'll give you ten hours.
If you're even a second late,
this bitch is dead.
The timer has started.
Sky hurts! Let Sky go!
What the hell are you whining about?
Come here!
Let go of Sky! Sky won't go. Let Sky go!
Sit there and look at the clock.
By ten hours...
if the police fail to rescue you,
you'll definitely be sent back
to your retard planet.
Inspector.
Sky's phone and bag
were found at the scene.
Everybody, listen up.
Find the pictures
from the scene of the incident.
No matter if it's a department store,
please bring them all.
Contact that TV show
and request for the tape urgently.
Understood.
Keep working.
- Sir.
- Save the hostage.
Inspector.
What have you done?
Huh?
I ordered you to admit about
arresting the wrong culprit.
But you challenged the murderer.
How could you do that while being live?
But it's the only way to lure him out.
Theory from your father's books, right?
So how is it now?
The PD couldn't be more embarrassing.
Huh?
Are you satisfied the the PD receiving
heavy backlash like this?
Have you ever read the online backlash?
How people have criticized
your competency?
How heavily the PD was reprimanded?
I know.
For this case...
I will take full responsibility
for everything.
It's certain, Inspector!
And if this time...
the hostage was even slightly injured,
you can find a new job.
Sir.
Please take a look.
Footage from CCTV cameras in Bangkok.
Track this car.
- Find out where it went. Go!
- Understood.
You can't enter, Miss Sookwan.
Miss Sookwan.
- You can't enter.
- Get out of the way.
I'm going to find that damn police officer.
Get out of the way.
- You can't enter. Calm down, Miss Sookwan.
- Get out of the way.
- You are not authorized to enter.
You said you would take care of my child.
What can police like you capable of then?
Only care about arresting the culprit,
without regard to other people's lives.
- I'm sorry.
- Are you?
Can your apology bring Sky back to me?
Just you wait and see if something happens to Sky.
I will not let you live in peace, just wait and see.
Ma'am! Ma'am!
-It's illegal to hurt an officer.
-Sergeant.
I won't just hurt you
I'll even kill you if anything happens to Sky.
Do not think that I do not dare.
Instead of blaming the inspector like this,
should you let him look for Sky?
We don't have much time left.
We still don't know where Sky is.
Sky and I...
We have a location tracker via GPS.
Sky...
Sky's phone.
It was found at the scene
where Sky had been kidnapped.
Is Sky safe?
- Turn up the sound.
- Right.
It's me.
The serial killer you guys are looking for.
How can I be sure?
That you are the real murderer
and not just calling to prank me.
Noppachai,
Nattha,
Isriya,
Anon, Phongsak,
Naphat.
Did I call out the names of the victims
in the correct order?
Can you cut out the other voices
and just keep the killer's voice alone?
Sure.
I want two files, one with the killer's voice.
Another with the ambient sound,
please separate it for me.
This is the most that can be cut, Inspector.
Lan, let's eat something.
I'm not hungry at all.
- Lan, but you haven't eaten anything since...
- You eat it.
If anything happens to Sky,
I will feel guilty for the rest of my life.
Lan.
- Land seems very worried about Sky.
- It's done, Inspector.
It's me.
The serial killer you guys are looking for.
Rewind, rewind it from the top.
- Can you turn up the volume?
- It's me.
This is the loudest.
Can you make it louder?
Right here, rewind.
Did I call out the names of the victims
in the correct order?
Ship.
The riverside.
The riverside here.
Too wide.
It's too wide. It's too wide. Too wide.
Rewind.
Sir.
It's me.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I'm not hungry, you eat it.
Are you not hungry
because you worried about Lan?
He probably isn't hungry.
He is worried about the hostage.
I think so.
Lan should be more worried about Sky individually
not as a hostage.
It's nothing.
Don't think too much.
Eat now.
Eat first.
Come on.
Just a bite.
Give it to me.
Which girl texted you?
-You should go home. It's past 11:00 p.m.
-Not a girl.
Shit!
Sis!
Smile for the camera.
Just smile for the fucked-up world.
The world you'll be living in
for just three more hours.
Smile a little.
I told you to smile.
You don't understand what I'm saying. Huh? Smile!
Stop.
Zoom in.
Zoom in further.
Zoom. Zoom in the window.
That's the Rama IX Bridge.
An extensive renovation.
If you see the top of the Rama IX Bridge,
it means the hostage is on the tall building.
There are many tall buildings
along the Chao Phraya River.
Which buildings?
Come on! Which buildings?
What did you buy, officer?
Here.
I give you.
Well, consider this as a teaching tool.
To teach me Morse Code.
Park here.
Where are you going? You're not wearing a helmet.
Give us some slack.
I went to buy cigarettes. My house is right in the alley.
Have you ever seen the person in this picture?
- I've never seen her.
- Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Go.
Hello, any updates?
Inspector.
Our patrol reported seeing strange blinking lights.
- From the buildings around the Rama IX Bridge.
- Tell them to send us the footage.
Send us the footage.
Dot-dot...
Dot-dash-dash-dash-dot-dot-dot.
Dot-dot-dot-dash-dash-dash-dot-dot-dot.
SOS.
Sky is asking for help!
Give me the coordinates.
Give me the coordinates quickly.
-Got it, Inspector.
-Let's go!
We have 45 minutes. Let's go!
What the hell are you playing, you bitch?
If you don't stop causing trouble,
you're going to die before your time.
In half an hour, prepare to die.
I'll livestream and kill you for the police.
Which floor did the light come from?
The light has stopped.
- How many floors does the building have?
- Twenty-six floors, sir.
Split up and search every floor and every room.
- Be careful of the hostage.
- Yes, sir! Let's go!
Aren't you? Aren't you? Aren't you?
If you're really competent,
come save her in time.
You have twelve hours.
Come here.
Sit down.
Hello, you dumbass police.
I warned you. If you are even a second late,
I won't spare her.
Prepare to die!
Fifteen.
Fourteen.
Thirteen.
Eleven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Sky.
It's okay, Sky.
You are safe now.
-Arrest him.
-Roger.
Sky.
Go, go!
Let go!
-Hey!
-Get in the car.
- Get in the car. Get in the car.
- Let me go!
Sky! Sky!
Sky? Are you alright? Are you hurt?
Are you hurt?
You're safe now.
Lan.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'll interrogate the culprit first.
So...
you admitted that
you are the real murderer.
Why the hell are you asking?
Are you afraid of arresting the scapegoat
and receiving backlash big time?
Your whole dumbass PD is so pathetic.
Even after the culprit has been caught,
you still don't know if you got the right one.
Fucking hilarious!
Fine.
So let's see.
The first victim you killed...
was Mr. Noppachai.
The second victim...
was Ms. Nattha.
The third victim was Ms. Isriya.
The fourth victim
was Mr. Anon.
The fifth victim
was Phra Phongsak.
And the sixth victim,
your latest victim
was Ms. Raphat.
Dumbass Noppachai,
stupid Nattha,
idiot Isriya,
moron Anon,
retard Phongsak,
bitch Raphat.
Do you think you can mess with me?
Why?
You still don't believe that I'm the murderer?
Fine.
Then tell me
about
the purpose of the killing
and the connection of each victim.
It's because I have Killer Genes.
The Genes that your father invented
and labeled me as a murderer
since the day I was born.
Here, I'm already doing it for his sake.
Are you happy now?
Are you telling me that you knitted
And then leave the yarn with every corpse
to connect and destroy Dr. Chonlathorn's reputation?
So, did it work?
Fine.
So let's see.
The riddle you left behind with each corpse.
The first corpse
was the bank employee.
The second corpse
was the receptionist in the mall.
The third corpse
was the convenience store cashier.
The fourth corpse
was a monk, and the last one was a sex worker.
The last piece of yarn.
You didn't leave any riddles.
Am I right?
Now, let me ask you this.
I've already admitted that I'm a murderer.
You can arrest me.
Arrest me so I can go on TV
and let everyone know what your father did to me.
- Why the fuck are you keep asking questions?
- Because you're not the real murderer!
I am the real serial killer who has killed six people.
If I can get out, I will kill.
-Kill, kill, kill them all.
-The real murderer...
left the riddles revealing that they have ten victims!
And in the riddle hidden in the last yarn
that was found with the monk
revealed that the next victim was supposed
to be a teacher, not a sex worker!
You're not the real murderer.
You're just a copycat killer.
No!
I'm not a copycat!
I'm the real yarn murderer!
I'm not a copycat! I'm not a copycat!
A copycat killer?
Yes, sir.
This culprit was not
the serial killer we are looking for.
So how can you be sure
they're not the same person?
Evidence from forensic science and forensics consistently reports a change in the method of murder.
This culprit killed a victim at another place
but left the body where we found it.
This pattern is different from
the real murderer's.
And there was no hidden riddle in the yarn,
we found with the body.
And most importantly, the victim who died
didn't match the hint in the previous riddle.
It means that the real killer is on the loose.
So what will you tell the people?
On behalf of the Royal Thai Police,
I would like to accept responsibility for the hasty conclusion of the serial murder case.
The PD would like to admit that...
he was not the real culprit.
But the PD did not remain indifferent.
In the part of the culprit
who killed Ms. Raphat,
kidnapped and attempted
to murder Miss Sky,
the PD would like to reaffirm that
he is not a real serial killer.
As for the real culprit,
they will definitely be arrested
and prosecuted according to the law.
Hey, here he comes!
I have a freaking Killer Genes!
I'm a human like you, right?
You dumbass Chonlathorn!
You ruined my life!
You made me a fucking monster in the society!
Whoever has this gene,
come out and kill them all.
Come out and kill! Be the monster
they label us to be!
Come on, come out! Everyone, come out!
How is the feedback now?
The people are divided into two groups.
Most of them agree with you.
Moreover, this copycat killer also has Killer Genes.
People have more faith in the law
that controls them.
And the group that disagrees?
The opposite group is made up of people
who really have killer genes,
but there aren't many of them because
they're under control and it's under curfew.
The rest don't have the Killer Genes,
but come out to demand freedom and rights
This group is becoming more violent
and influential every day.
How can you be sure
that if the law to control people
with Killer Genes is actually enforced,
our society will truly be free from crime?
It probably won't be completely crime-free.
I'd rather say it this way.
Suppose you were diagnosed
with a malignant tumor in your body.
It might not be a very big lump.
-But is it there, right?
-That's right.
Do you think you'll keep it or cut it out?
If you ask me like this,
I have to say that I will cut it out.
That's right.
But this is a country. We cannot exclude anyone.
So we need to control them.
Just think about it.
If we know that there are up to twenty percent
of the sixty million population
who are capable of committing crimes,
can we stand not helping to reduce the risk
of injuries, deaths, or loss?
Twenty percent.
Twenty percent is about twelve million people.
They're all over the country.
But this is just a draft of the Law.
We have to wait for the people
to vote in a referendum.
Shouldn't we let people choose
the society they want to live in?
Official referendum results
fifty-one percent of the people
accepting the draft of the Law to control the behavior
of those with Killer Genes.
Effective from April 25, 2000.
Requires all Thais to be tested for Killer Genes,
from newborns to high school children.
If the Killer Genes are found,
they must attend a special control school.
It is a boarding school.
They cannot study among
the other children.
Those in higher education
can choose to study at the institution they want.
But you are not allowed to study Medicine, Pharmacy,
Aviation Engineering, Royal Police Cadet Academy,
and all Military Academy.
Anyone with the Killer Genes must report to the police
at the police station near your home
every three months
If violated, the movement will be restricted
for a specified period.
Did I do something wrong?
What you did is right.
Time has proven that what you did is right.
You help the country be more peaceful
Look at your popularity rating.
Your IO is very good at their job.
I have to thank you very much, Miss Sookwan,
for communicating for us.
Otherwise, it would be
more difficult to communicate.
I would like to thank everyone as well,
for rescuing Sky.
But I still blame the police
for causing the incident.
How are you doing now, Sky?
You're not scared anymore, right?
Sky is fine now, but the officer is still not fine.
Does it hurt?
It doesn't hurt.
It was far from the heart.
"Far from the heart."
If it's close to your heart, will it hurt?
But when I got my hair pulled,
it was far from my heart,
I was hurt, it hurt a lot.
- Sky...
- Sweetheart...
You've talked too much.
Let's go back so the officer can do his job.
-Hello, Miss Sookwan.
-Hello.
Let's go. His girlfriend is here.
Miss Sookwan.
You probably misunderstood something.
Anya and I are close friends.
Yes, we are friends.
But it looks like a good match.
-Excuse me. Let's go.
-I'll see you out.
Sky, what are you doing, honey?
I saw you put the scotch tape on and off
since yesterday.
What is this?
Flashlight keychain.
If it's broken, just throw it away.
I will buy you a new one.
No, no, no, I won't throw it away.
This is what the police officer bought for Sky.
Sky.
It's okay, Sky.
Sky, you are safe now.
Sky.
You have really grown up.
Here, have some coffee.
What?
What a shame!
You were supposed to see
the person who was stabbed.
Instead, you got your heart stabbed with those words.
I get it now.
When people say that
the word "friend"
sometimes can cut the deepest.
Ouch! It hurts!
Go ahead, sis.
Stab me.
I will let you,
if that's gonna make you feel better.
Go ahead. Oh!
I...
I also see you as...
As...
a little brother.
It really hurts.
Do you still believe that
the killer is Miss Sookwan?
I don't believe it 100 percent.
But I feel that Ms. Sookwan
has a strange attitude.
It's like she's hiding something.
But there are still no other clues.
Would you like me to continue following her?
If that's the case, I'll follow Sookwan tomorrow.
I will try my best to get into her house too.
Order all units to thoroughly patrol
every school in Bangkok,
especially Arunpanya School.
I believe the next victim will come from this school.
Yes, sir. I'll go take care of it right away.
Just a sec, Sergeant.
If you have the chance,
I'd like you to ask Rapee
whether she remembers anyone
who had issues with Sookwan and Sky.
Alright.
Why do the police think that the murderer
would kill people in my school?
Er... Don't worry about it. Leave it to the police.
Tell me, I want to know.
Who is the murderer going to kill?
I don't know either.
I only know that they are a teacher.
But there are many teachers in many schools
around the country.
The Inspector had the officers
keep an eye on everywhere,
but he had me pay special attention
to your school.
See?
How can I not be worried?
Tell me so that I will be careful.
Is it related to Miss Sookwan?
That day, your boss came to ask me
about Sky and Miss Sookwan.
It's about her, right?
But from everything you've told me,
there aren't any teachers
who had an issue with Sookwan, right?
Right.
There aren't any.
Tomorrow, I have a special class
with Miss Sookwan too.
I'm scared.
Don't be. I have to follow Sookwan anyway.
Okay?
Go on.
Sky.
What are you doing?
Sky...
Sky is waiting for...
Hello, Miss Sookwan.
-Sky.
-Hello, officer.
You are late today.
You usually arrive at around 8:30,
but now you're 15 minutes late.
There's a bit of a traffic jam today.
That's alright.
Please, come inside the house.
Are you letting me into your house today?
You are not a stranger,
not even an acquaintance.
You saved Sky's life, so Sky considers
the police officer a friend.
Friends can enter their homes. Please come in.
Um, that's not good.
A man and a woman are alone together.
I think it's inappropriate.
But he is Sky's friend now.
-Friends can enter their friends' houses.
-Sky
I think it's better for the Inspector to
watch over you from the outside.
You'd better get in the house now.
And don't go anywhere.
I will be back in the evening. Come on.
Get into the house. Go in.
Very good, take it slow.
Please take it easy.
Take it easy. Focus.
Oh.
How about this? Are you helping each other?
Hey, is this table okay? Is it okay? Okay.
But from everything you've told me,
there aren't any teachers
who had an issue with Sookwan, right?
Sky is a such problematic kid, Director.
No one can communicate with her.
No matter what I ask, she doesn't answer.
Even when we talk, she doesn't even look at me.
I told her to look at me but she wouldn't.
Have you talked to the child's parents yet?
We talked, but she cried and begged me
not to expel her kid.
Because it is very difficult for her
to find a school for Sky.
It's obvious that Sky
is not ready to live with other children.
Director, please believe me.
Please expel this kid.
Ms. Rapeephan,
What's wrong?
Why do you look so pale?
Um, no, it's nothing.
I'll go to the bathroom first.
Please take care of the students.
What? You're the one
who suggested expelling Sky from school?
Well, at that time,
it was too much to bear.
And no one knows
what is autism,
and how to cope with autism.
It was really stressful at that time.
I'm scared.
That's alright.
Don't be scared.
At that time, besides you
and the former director,
does anyone else know about this?
Then it's okay.
Keep this a secret, don't tell anyone, understand?
Go back to the classroom
and do your job as usual.
Don't let Sookwan suspect you at all.
What are you looking for, officer?
Oh.
Nothing.
It just so happens that I...
I see that your house is beautiful,
so I want to look around.
Can you give me a tour of the house?
Of course. Sure.
Sky will take you on a tour
of every corner.
Welcome.
Please.
This is Sky's house.
This is Sky's TV. And this is Sky's chair.
This is Mother and Sky's dining table.
What are you looking for, officer?
Can I help you find it?
I'm not looking for anything.
Your house is beautiful, so I look around.
Please continue the tour.
This is my mother's kitchen.
And what is this room, Sky?
Storage room.
Can you please let me see this room?
There's nothing worth watching.
There are so many of my mom's things, it's so messy.
Oh, and the bathroom, Sky. I'd like to use the bathroom.
Do you need to pee? Or do you need to poop?
Er...
I have to poop.
The bathroom is over there, officer.
Please feel free to use it.
Then you can wait for me in the living room.
Feel free to take a poop, officer.
Thank you.
Hey, I'm following Sookwan. What are you doing?
I'm preparing to teach my last class, darling.
There's also a tutoring session this evening.
I'm scared, baby.
Don't be.
I will not let Sookwan slip my sight.
If Sookwan is the real killer,
then I must know first.
After you off work, I'll pick you up.
Don't go anywhere alone.
Shit!
Huh?
Miss Sookwan disappeared.
I'm sorry.
Sky and I...
We have a location tracker via GPS.
Wait a moment, Sergeant.
- Sky. Sky.
- Yes?
Can I borrow your phone?
My phone's battery is dead.
Sure.
But don't use it too long
or the battery will run out.
Yes, I won't take long.
Sergeant.
- Miss Sookwan is at Arunpanya School.
- Huh?
Oh no, Rapee!
Sergeant, Sergeant.
Sky, thank you. Thank you.
Come on!